[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 3]
She's arrived home safely.
Where are we going?
To work.
Isn't the Human-faced Owl already dead?
[Duan's Mansion]
Father is back.
Father.
Father?
Father!
What happened?
Banxia.
Father, what was that sound just now?
I accidentally fell down.
It's nothing serious.
You fell?
Where are you hurt?
I'm alright.
Why are you...
Still up?
I was hungry, so I went to get some food.
Father, when did you come back?
Just now.
I just came back.
A lot of things happened at home.
Do you know about them?
It's that new sister-in-law of mine.
I'll go inside and talk to you in detail.
Banxia.
It's so late now.
Let's talk
tomorrow.
I've been busy
organizing manuscripts all day.
I'm quite exhausted.
I want to sleep early.
Are you really alright?
Banxia.
What could possibly be wrong with me?
I'm just
really tired.
Rest early then.
Grandmother has been asking about you these days.
Remember to
go see her early tomorrow morning.
It's been a long time
since I last dyed your hair.
Tomorrow when you have time,
I'll dye your hair for you.
Okay.
I'll go back then.
Banxia.
It's dark.
Be careful.
Got it.
After I leave,
don't go back to reading.
Got it.
It's midnight. Safe and sound.
What's your name?
My name is Manying.
My Lady.
W-What's wrong?
Did you have another nightmare?
Did you dream about Manying?
Tingzhou.
Do you think Manying might be real?
Here we go again.
My Lady.
The physician has told you
it was just a dream.
You also dreamed about things like
the Bat Spirit
and the Black Panther Demon.
How could it be real?
But if
there really are demons in this world,
does that mean
my dream was real,
the people inside my dream are real,
and Manying is also a real person?
My Lady.
It's so early in the morning.
Instead of thinking about this,
maybe you should think about
how to respond to Elder Madam.
Master has been gone for days.
Elder Madam is obviously angry.
My father has come back.
He's back?
When?
Last night.
Go get me some water.
I'll wash up and go see my father.
Okay.
Clean this area more thoroughly.
Alright, give it another wipe.
Mr. Xu.
My Lady.
Is my father inside?
Has the Second Master come back?
Make way!
This way.
Yingheng.
How could this happen?
I...
M... My father...
Why is my father here?
This mansion
was originally a residence affiliated with
the Yunqing Trading Company.
The company usually earns some money
through renting out properties.
Recently,
Uncle Yingheng rented this place
and has been living here for several days straight.
Last night between 9 to 11 p.m.,
the woodshed caught fire.
The fire was huge,
and it spread to this courtyard very fast.
I guess Uncle Yingheng...
Had nowhere to escape,
so he hid back in the study.
In the end,
he was suffocated to death in here.
Yingheng!
Yingheng...
Yanqiu.
That's impossible.
I saw my father
at midnight last night.
My father had lost a lot of weight
and looked haggard at that time.
I...
I noticed he has grown a lot of gray hair,
and he agreed
to let me dye his hair today.
It's true!
Banxia.
He's already passed away.
No! Trust me!
I saw him last night.
He couldn't be dead.
Banxia!
The fact is already right in front of us.
You still won't believe it?
Something must be wrong.
My father is not dead.
I saw him.
He can't be dead.
He's not dead.
This can't be.
My father is not dead.
There must be something wrong somewhere.
What on earth are you doing?
Luring the sound eel out.
The sound eel is the Human-faced Owl's companion demon.
Since the Human-faced Owl died,
the sound eel will definitely avenge her.
Didn't you say
the sound eel was born with poor eyesight,
but it has exceptional hearing
and loves beautiful sounds?
Then I can definitely lure it here
with my flute.
You call this a beautiful sound?
Isn't it beautiful?
If you don't play the flute,
it may come faster.
It's here?
Be careful.
Chi Xue!
[Sound Eel]
Chi Xue.
Cut the rope!
You can't run away now, can you?
What a small world.
We meet again, guys.
What are you doing here?
I hope I'm not ruining
any of your fun, Physician Jiu.
What do you want?
Nothing.
It's just the weather is nice,
so I came out for a walk.
Are you going back to the city?
How about we go together?
It's out of your way.
It's not.
No matter where you want to go, Physician Jiu,
it's on my way.
Chi Xue.
Let's go.
Hey, let's go together.
W-Was this place robbed?
My Lady.
Why is it so messy here?
Was Father planning to travel far?
M-My Lady!
Come here!
Look.
Here.
Look at this.
Why is this mirror
not reflecting us?
[Duan's Mansion]
My poor girl.
Your mother died when you were still little,
and now, you've lost your father too.
How should you live
alone in this world
from now on?
Grandmother,
please don't be sad.
My father might still be alive.
At midnight the day before yesterday,
I saw my father come home with my own eyes.
He was right in his room.
He seemed to be in good spirits at that time,
but he did look a bit tired.
He said it was because
he hadn't rested well
since he'd been organizing manuscripts.
Therefore, I didn't talk to him for long.
On my way back to my room,
I heard the watchman beating his drum.
He clearly struck it three times.
But the government file stated that
my father died before 11 p.m.
Think about it.
If he had died before 11 p.m.,
how could he have come home
at midnight?
There must be something fishy about this.
My father must still be alive.
This... This...
Could it be she ran into a ghost?
Banxia.
I know you're feeling heartbroken,
but...
Uncle.
I'm not saying this
out of excessive sadness.
You all know that
my eyes have been different
from those of ordinary people since childhood.
If this were caused by ghosts or demons,
I'd definitely be able to tell.
Uncle Yingheng lived in the east courtyard,
while you live in the west courtyard.
The two sides are very far apart.
Why didn't you sleep that night
and went to Uncle Yingheng's room instead?
I didn't go there from my room.
Actually, I saw the lights were on
in my father's room when I came back
from outside.
So I went to check.
At such a late hour,
where did you go?
I...
I went to see a friend.
You live in Yuanzhou year-round.
Why do you have friends in Nanyang City?
I'm not lying.
Mr. Xu.
I saw Mr. Xu changing the candles
when I came back.
That's when
his hand got scalded.
I saw him first,
and then my father.
Young Master.
My hand was indeed
scalded when
changing the candles
the night before last.
It was exactly at midnight.
My Lady.
I didn't see you
when I changed the candles.
I came back too late.
I didn't want to be scolded by Grandmother,
so I hid myself.
Mr. Xu's hand injury is not a secret.
This still can't prove
what you said is true.
I know what I said is hard to believe,
but think about it carefully.
Don't you find it strange?
My father and I came back this time
for Yanqiu's marriage.
But as soon as he came back,
he rented a mansion outside,
and he didn't come back often.
as if he was
hiding from something.
Uncle Yingheng asked me to rent that mansion for him.
He said it was to organize manuscripts peacefully,
not to avoid anyone.
The weather and the life
are both unpredictable.
Banxia.
I know it's hard for you to accept
Uncle Yingheng's death right now.
But now that it's come to this,
you must stay strong.
Tingzhou, the mirror.
I found this mirror
in my father's room.
It can only reflect objects,
not people.
I went to the fire scene
at Penglai Alley
and found a mirror
which is exactly the same as this one.
Isn't this suspicious enough?
This...
How could this be?
No way.
It clearly couldn't
reflect anything yesterday.
Tingzhou, you saw it too, right?
Yes.
I saw it too.
It couldn't reflect people.
I know.
It must have been a powerful demon
using a deceptive spell.
That's why we couldn't see it.
I know a demon hunter.
-We can…
-Banxia!
Tingzhou.
Help your lady back to her room.
Why?
Why can't you
believe me even for once?
I'll take you to Jishi Clinic later
to see Physician Sun.
I'm not sick!
I said my father is still alive!
These are all caused by demons!
Demons?
Demons again?
How come only you
can see those demons?
Why can't I see any of them?
You have.
You all have!
It's just that you couldn't see through
her disguise.
Don't tell me you still think that
Sister-in-law was abducted by a villain.
She's a demon,
a Human-faced Owl,
with a monkey's body and a dog's tail,
which likes to eat human throats.
She approached you just to...
Shut up!
Sir, welcome.
Please, come in.
Mr. Zhang.
Sir, please come inside.
Please, come in.
This is your first time here, right, Sir?
Come on. This way.
Have another drink.
Is this your first time here?
Where did you come from, you brute?
How dare you hit me?
Mr. Song.
Mr. Song!
Why are you leaving?
Sir,
Chuntao
already has a guest today.
How about
I arrange some other girl
for you?
I won't disturb you any further.
Chuntao.
Take good care of this gentleman here.
Sir.
Your bamboo hat...
Keep playing!
In the future,
if you encounter any trouble,
you can come to Guangping City to find me.
My Lady.
It's time to take your medicine.
They don't believe me,
and you don't, either?
Of course I believe you, My Lady.
But what's the use
of me being the only one
who believes you, My Lady?
All others, including Young Master, don’t believe you.
I don't need them.
We've been looking for so long and still haven't found him.
Do you think he might have run far away?
No.
He must be nearby.
Why?
Sound eels are different from other demons.
For him, beautiful sounds
are both food
and medicine.
Since he's injured,
he'll definitely search for
beautiful sounds in the city
to heal himself.
He just won't leave us alone.
What should we do?
She's been playing the whole night.
Why haven't they come out yet?
Exactly, Madame.
Madame.
How about we report it to the government?
Right.
Madame, it's a matter of life and death.
It's a matter of life and death, Madame.
Right.
Alright.
Let's report this to the government.
Qiusheng!
Come here.
Come on.
You're the fastest.
Go to the government office
and ask Chief Constable Song
to bring enough people over.
Go quickly.
Yes.
Why are you so flustered?
Do you know Chief Constable Song?
Yes, I do.
Come with me and report to the government.
Report to the government?
Let's go. Someone is causing trouble.
May I ask who you are...
Quite the refined entertainment, isn't it?
If she keeps playing, she'll bleed out.
Young lady?
You've woken up?
Wearing a bamboo hat indoors,
don't you feel stifled?
Run while you still can.
You're really getting uglier and uglier.
Chi Xue.
Take it away.
I received a letter from your fiancé.
He knows what happened to your father.
He said he'd come to Nanyang
as soon as he finishes his work.
I've inquired about him.
He's a good guy.
Pretty talented.
Uncle Yingheng had good taste.
Banxia.
I've got news about Manniang.
Do you still remember
that throat-slitting scoundrel
in the city recently?
Guangping has sent an official arrest warrant.
The scoundrel on the portrait
is Manniang.
Do you believe it?
I will go investigate it.
So you still don't believe it.
Of course I don't believe it.
She's just a weak woman.
I'll continue to investigate.
But regardless,
there are no demons in this world,
and that's a fact.
So,
you should stop overthinking it.
Now,
although Uncle Yingheng is gone,
we will take good care of you.
I understand.
It's raining.
Let me walk you back.
No need.
I can go back by myself.
Go back and rest early.
My Lady.
I've finished packing.
Okay.
Let's go.
[To Yanqiu]
It's raining so heavily.
Mister.
Is there a ferry dock ahead
where there are boats to Guangping every day?
Do you know
when that boat comes?
Every day at noon.
Are you taking a boat to Guangping?
The boat only comes once a day.
It's raining so heavily.
I'm afraid you won't make it today.
Wait until tomorrow.
My Lady.
How about we go back?
When will this rain stop?
Let's go.
[Guangping City]
What should we do about him?
When the full moon arrives,
I'll deal with him.
Alright.
You're a demon yourself too.
Why are you so rude
to someone of your own kind?
I'm nothing like him.
He's so stupid.
If I were him
and encountered such a formidable opponent like you,
I would have probably disappeared by now.
Companion demons are very loyal.
Once they've chosen their master,
they'll never regret it even if they die a hundred times.
I killed the Human-faced Owl.
Of course he wants to avenge his master
by staying close to his enemy
and waiting for the right time.
This sound eel
is actually quite loyal.
Keep a close eye on it.
♫A familiar figure♫
♫Becomes clear in the haze♫
♫Yet it's out of reach♫
♫Your earnest reminders♫
♫And words of concern♫
Xuanye, you're back.
He came back pretty quickly this time.
♫They've woven and colored the time we shared♫
Yes.
But he still didn't make it in time for your wedding.
It's okay.
There will be a next time.
♫Traces of bond♫
Maybe there'll even be a third time.
♫With a sigh, we bid farewell♫
♫Keeping you company, and seeing you off on a long journey♫
So you know to come back?
Look at these.
How long have you been wearing these shoes?
They're so dirty.
I'll wash them for you.
♫You're the same as before♫
♫And I'm still following closely behind♫
Xuanye.
Now I finally know
what Moon Bugs like to eat.
♫Remember it day and night♫
They like to eat lamb lung soup.
Don't put any oil, salt, sauce or vinegar in it.
Just boil it in plain water
for a few hours.
♫One side is the past♫
They'll finish it in a blink of an eye.
♫Where you lingered♫
Just wait.
Wait for my Moon Bugs
♫The other is the unforgettable♫
to grow big and strong.
I guarantee that if you carry them with you,
♫Dream of mine♫
even a century-old demon
will be terrified and run away.
♫A fallen leaf, a drop of wine♫
♫Each drop into my heart♫
Did your trip this time go well?
♫A moment of memory, an illusion♫
♫One side is the past♫
Son.
♫Where you lingered♫
People can be good or bad,
and the same goes for demons.
You can't generalize.
♫The other is the unforgettable♫
Got it?
♫Dream of mine♫
Yes.
♫A fallen leaf, a drop of wine♫
♫Each drop into my heart♫
♫A moment of memory, an illusion♫
♫A segment of reminiscence engraved for a lifetime♫
The starry sky is really bright tonight.
So delicious.
[Zhang's Mansion]
Between 7 to 9 p.m.,
the moon hangs low.
Pear Fairy, listen to my words.
I'm not blinded by money,
nor am I seeking a good marriage.
Between 9 to 11 p.m.,
the moonlight is cold.
Pear Fairy, come to my courtyard.
I'm not lamenting in front of the mirror,
nor am I foolishly seeking to extend my life.
At midnight,
the moonlight is dim.
Pear Fairy, listen to my wishes.
First wish: the flowers bloom again,
life and death I bear.
Second wish: I offer my bones and blood,
just to be young again.
Eat it.
Come on, eat it.
Come on.
Eat it.
Come on, eat it.
It's midnight. Safe and sound.
Chi Xue!
Chi Xue.
Go back.
In a minute.
Hurry up.
Boss, on credit.
Manniang's sister-in-law.